

Erik Lopez-Alfaro

Software Developer



(206) 898-4561



eriklopezalfaro@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/eriklopezalfaro github.com/eriklopezalfaro

www.eriklopezalfaro.com



SKILLS

Technical Skills:

- o HTML5/CSS3
- o Python2/Python3
- o Django Framework
- o Git/ GitHub
- o Terminal
- JavaScript/ jQuery

Other Skills:

- o Intercultural communication
- o Time management
- Problem-solving

EDUCATION

Associate of Applied Science Computing and Software Development

Lake Washington Institute of Technology - Kirkland, WA September 2019 — June 2021

Coding Bootcamp Certificate

Coding Dojo – Seattle, WA July 2017 – October 2017

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Fluent)

English (Fluent)

ABOUT ME

Disciplined software developer with strong work ethic that's able to create fast and optimal solutions and provide a creative mind for front-end web development, also provides +7 years of Customer Service experience to provide exceptional customer/ user satisfaction. Developed a Personal website portfolio, ecommerce webapp, and a local cleaning business website. Passionate about full stack development and software architecture.

PROJECTS

YDS Professional Cleaning Services

Website for a cleaning services company based in Bellevue that is built on the Django Framework and provides informational tabs with a contact page that allows potential clients to email them.

Vintage Soccer Ecommerce

Ecommerce website that serves as a marketplace for older vintage soccer jerseys that you cannot buy in stores ranging from club jerseys to country jerseys. Uses the Django Framework to implement a user sign up/login app with and has add to cart functionality. Displays blog posts and reviews using Swiper.

EXPERIENCE

Shipper/ Customer Service

T&A Supply Co./ Kent, WA/ March 2018 - Present

- Providing well detailed flooring samples for our sales team, product partners, and long-time customers. Includes in person visits and via mail.
- Exceptional service to all clients and partners helping maintain and improve professional business relationships, this includes efficiently helping find correct flooring samples to match the needs of their project.
- Shipping pallets of flooring related samples and new flooring line launches to all our representatives at all our branches in a timely fashion.

Customer Service/ Sales

Best Buy/ Bellevue, WA/ May 2015- June 2017

- Communication and teamwork with the rest of my specialty division team in Pacific Kitchen and Sales producing clear and efficient workflow.
- Managed and organized all orders for our sales team into separate folders and maintained them up to date
- Created orders and set up deliveries for our clients using multiple systems
- Handled client concerns/issues and made pre/post-delivery calls to clients for ultimate customer experience